《末世》前情回顧
Previously on Revolution...
你從來沒讓我按照自己的意愿做過事
You have never once let me do things my way.
如果你想得到一個機會  我給你
If you want a shot, you got one.
大家快跑
Everybody, run, now!
是芥子氣
It's mustard gas!
我們今天失去了二十個手下
We lost 20 men today.
邁爾斯  唯一重要的事
The only thing that matters, Miles,
就是打敗這些人
is beating these guys.
我加入
I'm in.
邁爾斯  怎么回事
Miles, what's this?
將堿液和水混合  就能中和芥氣
You mix lye and water, and it neutralizes mustard gas.
我們現在沒辦法和他們對抗了  邁爾斯
Now we got nothing to fight 'em with, Miles!
瑪麗恩  這是芥氣
Marion, this is mustard gas.
愛國者對我們使用這東西
Patriots are using this stuff on us.
你想讓我做什么
Well, what do you want me to do?
沒人能比你更能盯著圖魯門
Nobody has better eyes on Truman than you.
告訴我們他想干什么
Tell us what he's up to.
你是納米機器人
You're the nano.
按我們說的做  會把普里西拉還給你的
Just do what we say, and you will get Priscilla back.
同時  你要做我們的指導
In the meantime, you will be our guide,
而且你不能告訴任何人
and you won't tell anyone.
你要去哪兒
Where are you going?
我們不需要邁爾斯
We don't need Miles.
你想要殺死我  湯姆
You want to kill me, Tom?
那就殺死我
Then kill me.
放開這孩子
You're gonna let the boy go.
我不想殺你
I don't want to kill you.
我們還有活兒要忙呢
You and me-- we've got work to do.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
什么活兒
What kind of work?
翻譯  冰藍  米蘇
校對  油炸電風扇  米蘇
朱莉婭死了
Julia's dead.
時間軸  JimmyBeck  兜兜兜爹  aaaBao
很遺憾
I'm sorry.
后期  阿小小海
愛國者們殺了她  因為我沒法抓住你
The patriots killed her because I couldn't catch you.
總監  米蘇
他們本來也不會放了她的  湯姆
They were never gonna let her go, Tom.
你知道的  對吧
You know that, right?
杰森也是這么說的
That's what Jason said.
現在怎么辦
So what now?
我要一次一個
I am gonna take the patriots down
干掉愛國者
one corpse at a time.
我要走小道去華盛頓
I am gonna cut a path to Washington
對著總統的頭開一槍
and put a bullet in the President's face.
讓謝爾曼將軍的遠征
Make Sherman's March
感覺像是十公里長跑
feel like a 10k fun run.
你對這種事感興趣嗎
Is that the sort of work that you'd be interested in?
正和我的胃口
That is music to my ears.
-那邁爾斯呢  -邁爾斯
- What about Miles? - Miles...
你覺得邁爾斯
You--you think Miles
會不同意那樣做嗎
might have a problem with that?
他不愿意放手一搏
He's not willing to do what it takes,
和我們不一樣
not like us.
十點半前裝滿兩個水柜
Have both tanks filled by 10:30.
清潔儀表
Clean the gauges.
232號出去打水
2-3-2 going out for water.
開門
Open the gate.
你是喬嗎
You Joe?
是的
Yes.
我知道你們是誰
And I know who you are.
你確定沒人看見你們嗎
You sure no one saw you?
我們懂行的
We know what we're doing.
相信我們
Trust us.
也許瑪麗恩說你們沒問題
Well, maybe Marion says you're okay,
但我不認識你們
but I don't know you.
我們也是  哥們  臂章不錯
Same here, buddy. Nice armband.
我們怎么知道你不會告發我們
How do we know you're not gonna turn us in?
-也許我該這樣做  -好了
- Well, maybe I should. - All right.
瑪麗恩說你沒問題
Marion says you're okay.
瑪麗恩說我們沒問題
Marion says we're okay.
我們都沒問題
We're all okay.
你看見芥氣了嗎
Have you seen the mustard gas or not?
有多少桶
How many barrels we talking about?
就一桶
One.
一桶  你說就一桶是什么意思
One? What do you mean, one?
仔細看朝著基地那個車廂的尾部
Look close at the end of the car toward the base.
我看見了
Yeah, I see it.
黃十字
Yellow cross,
他們給芥氣的符號
their little code for mustard gas.
一罐車都是
Whole damn tanker car full of it.
-這是個問題  -你覺得呢
- That's a problem. - You think?
你知道誰能在這件事上幫忙嗎
You know who would've been helpful with all this?
門羅
Monroe.
他現在可能已經往北走了一半路
Yeah, well, he's probably halfway north by now,
這就是說  不幸的是  我們只能靠你了
which means, sadly, we're left with you.
銘記烈士
午餐吃什么
What's for lunch?
和往常一樣  喜好不會變
Same as always. The man likes what he likes.
我知道你很忙  布萊恩  你去忙你的
I know you're busy, Brian. You go on.
-我來布置  -是  女士
- Let me set up. - Yes, ma'am.
-我最喜歡的  -來吃吧
- My favorite. - Come on and eat.
等等
Wait.
看來你沒找到他
Take it you didn't find him.
已經過了24小時
It's been 24 hours.
到處都沒看到亞倫和普里西拉
There's no sign of Aaron or Priscilla anywhere.
我們得走了
We have to go.
我們得找他們  所有人都是
We have to look for them, all of us.
我明白  這是個問題
I get it. It's a problem.
但不是我們唯一的問題
But it's not our only problem.
有麻煩了
We got a problem.
你確定照片里是卡弗將軍
You're sure it was General Carver in that picture.
他是德州總統  我知道他的樣子
He's the President of Texas. I know what he looks like.
是他的照片  還有黃十字標志
It was his picture and that yellow cross symbol,
計劃  日程
plans, schedules,
還有圈出的日期  就是明天
and a circled date, tomorrow's date.
這一切真是太糟糕了
Well, that all adds up to awful.
你覺得怎樣
So what do you think?
我覺得他們要把毒氣運往奧斯汀
I think they're sending the gas to Austin.
愛國者們以前試圖謀殺過卡弗
Patriots tried to kill Carver once before.
現在他們只是加倍加注
Now they're just doubling down.
往首都投毒氣  殺死幾千人
Gas the capitol. Kill a couple thousand people.
栽贓給加州  打造珍珠港事件
Pin it on California. Stage their own Pearl Harbor.
那沒法阻止了
Then there's no stopping it.
德州和加州宣戰  消滅對方
Texas and California go to war, wipe each other out.
愛國者們接管剩下的事
Patriots take over the rest.
我們能中和毒氣嗎
Can we neutralize the gas?
我們沒法偷運那么多堿液
We'll never sneak that much lye into the yard.
但也許...
But maybe...
瑞秋  你得獨自去找
Rachel, you're gonna have to find Aaron
亞倫和普里西拉
and Priscilla alone.
-抱歉  -那你呢
- Sorry. - What about you?
我們
Us?
我們要偷一輛火車
We're gonna steal a train.
末           世
第二季  第二十一集
放松點
Easy.
-他們知道你走了嗎  -當然
- They know you're gone? - Course they do.
我出來找馬車  為了一次大搶劫
I'm out getting a wagon for the big heist.
搶劫
Heist?
我們要偷一輛火車
We're stealing a train
掛著一個裝滿芥氣的罐車
with a tanker car full of yellow cross.
湯姆  你愿不愿意駕駛一輛
Tom, how would you feel about driving a tanker car
裝滿芥氣的罐車  直接開向華盛頓中心
filled with mustard gas straight into the heart of D.C.
把毒氣灌進這些王八蛋的喉嚨里
And shove it down the throats of these sons of bitches?
你說芥氣時就吸引到我了
You had me at mustard gas.
瑪麗恩回來了
Marion's back.
她帶來了你要的人
She brought the people you asked for.
這就是我的抵抗力量嗎
This is my resistance?
我告訴你  我需要六個壯漢
I told you I needed six good people
來偷那輛貨車
to steal that train.
你給我帶來了麥莉和比利·雷
You bring me Miley and Billy Ray.
大部分人都不喜歡你  我盡了最大努力
Most people don't like you. It's all I could get.
還不夠好
Well, it's not good enough.
我們可以出入火車場
We can get in and out of that train yard,
這比你們能做的多多了
which is a hell of a lot more than you can do.
你知道怎么打架
You know how to fight
或者殺人嗎
or kill a man?
回家去吧  我想別的辦法
Go home. I'll figure something else--
什么  不行  等等  我們必須幫忙
What? No, wait. Look, we got to help.
你必須讓我們幫忙  明白吧
You got to let us help, you understand me?
鎮上的其他人都支持愛國者
Everybody else in town is waving a patriot flag.
你為什么這么熱心要加入
Why you so hot to join up?
邁爾斯  這是喬·馬修斯
Miles, this is Joe Matthews.
他兒子迪倫被愛國者害死了
He lost his son Dillon to the patriots.
那是我兒子
It's my boy.
她的哥哥
Her brother.
他去了他們的訓練營
He went out to their boot camp.
瑪麗恩告訴我  他們搞壞了孩子們的腦袋
Marion told me how they scrambled those kids' heads.
他們對他做了什么
They did something to him.
我們再也沒見過迪倫
We never saw Dillon again.
我想你們得接受
I guess you'll have to do.
那是你在奧斯汀
You know, that's the father
殺死的孩子的父親
of the kid you shot in Austin.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你要告訴他嗎
You gonna tell him?
先等我們搞定這事吧
Not until we get through this mess,
但是我會告訴他的
but, yeah, I'm gonna tell him.
邁爾斯  成功不了的  和他們一起不行
Miles, this is never gonna work, not with these people.
查理  我沒法改變我做過的事
Charlie, I can't change the things I've done
或者是過去的我
or who I was when I did them.
我能改變的就是從今以后做的事
All I can change is what I do from here on out.
所以你要相信他
So you're gonna trust him.
我的直覺在咆哮  不要
I got every instinct in me screaming no...
但我盡量想象一個好人的做法
But I'm trying to picture what a good guy would do...
好人會相信他的
And a good guy would trust him.
好吧
All right.
-做個好人真不爽  -是啊
- Being a good guy sucks. - Yeah, it really does.
-我不想回去  -瑪麗恩
- I don't want to go back. - Marion.
我想到艾德做的事
When I think about what Ed's done,
他打算做的事
what's he's planning to do--
我是說  天啊  我還打算嫁給他
I mean, my god, I was gonna marry him.
我不是個好演員
I'm not that good an actor.
他會知道不對勁
He's gonna know something's wrong.
如果你不回去  他絕對會知道
If you don't go back, he'll definitely know.
我很害怕  吉恩
I'm scared, Gene.
我們知道你很愚蠢  會做正確的事
We know that you're dumb enough to do the right thing
又很聰明  肯定會為此害怕
and smart enough to be terrified by it.
你能做到  瑪麗恩
You can do this, Marion.
-瑞秋  -亞倫
- Rachel? - Aaron?
你得走
You got to go.
-這是怎么回事  -我們都沒事
- What the hell is going on? - We're all good.
一切正常  但你得走了
Everything is good, but you got to go.
真的嗎  你沒事嗎
Really? Really, you're good?
瑞秋  拜托  你得...
Rachel, please, you got to--
瑞秋
Rachel,
歡迎來到我們家
Welcome to our home.
她來了  都看到了
Well, she's here. She's seen everything.
你不妨告訴她
You might as well tell her.
告訴我什么
Tell me what?
普里西拉是納米機器人
Priscilla's the nano.
不好意思  什么意思
I'm sorry. What does that mean?
意思就是它們霸占了她的身體
It means that they've taken over her body
把真正的普里西拉
and they're keeping the real Priscilla
關在她自己的頭腦里
locked away inside her head.
就是這樣
So that happened.
我們終于能聊一聊了
It's good we can finally speak,
瑞秋  面對面的
Rachel, face-to-face.
你和這些人在這里做什么
What are you doing with these people in here?
我想讓你理解
I want you to understand.
跟我來
Come with me.
這個月很不可思議
It's been a weird month.
地板在動
The floor is moving.
不  我們有一間鼠屋
No, we have a rat room.
我先用老鼠做實驗
When I started with the rats,
效果一樣
it was the same thing,
多次反復實驗  多次犯錯
lots of trial and error, lots of mistakes.
但現在你瞧
But now look at them,
自發形成了一個體系
A system in agreement with itself.
他們很滿足
They are content.
我對螢火蟲也做了同樣的事情
I did the same with the fireflies.
我也想這樣對你們
I want to do the same with you.
你瘋了
That is insane.
抱歉  但是你們這種物種才瘋了
I'm sorry, but it's your species that's insane.
這是你們的典型特征
It's your defining characteristic,
你們對彼此造成傷害
the way you all inflict pain on each other,
冷酷無情地進食  殺人  達到高潮
this relentless drive to eat, kill, and to orgasm,
就像沒毛的猩猩
like hairless chimpanzees.
-我好心痛  -你沒有心
- It breaks my heart. - You don't have a heart.
我有感情
I have feelings.
我成熟  進化  你們也可以
I've grown, evolved, and you can too.
我可以幫你們  修復你們
I can help you, fix you.
人類的大腦很復雜
The human brain is complicated,
硬件更復雜
the hardware more complex,
但只要時間足夠  我就可以升級它
but with enough time, I can upgrade it.
升級
Upgrade it.
我可以讓你們快樂
I can make you happy.
你好大膽子
How dare you?
你對那些人  對普里西拉
What you've done to those people,
所做的事情  天知道你還對
to Priscilla, and god knows what hell
還讓亞倫經歷了怎樣的痛苦
you've put Aaron through.
你只不過是我該死的科學項目而已
You're my damn science project.
為什么制造我的人那么害怕我
Why are the ones who made me so afraid of what I am?
我愛你們倆
I love you both.
我絕不會厭惡你們
I will never turn away from you.
永遠不會
Never.
-早上好  -檢查馬車
- Morning. - Wagon check, please.
沒事的
Oh, it's okay.
比爾  另一個守衛  他認識我的
Bill, the other guard, he knows me.
檢查馬車  謝謝
Wagon check, please.
都是好吃的  對吧
Good enough to eat, right?
我的背
My back.
彼得斯在找你
Peters was asking for you
在440車廂那邊
over by the tender car on the 440.
告訴他我很忙
Tell him I'm busy.
好  不過他說是關于鍋爐泄露的事情
Okay, he said something about the boiler having a leak, though.
該死
Damn it.
彼得斯
Peters.
按我們說的做
Do what we say,
也許你還能回去吃晚飯
you might make it home for dinner.
現在  你快讓火車發動起來
Now, we're gonna need you to get this train moving.
鍋爐還不夠熱
The boiler-- it's not hot enough yet.
那就讓它夠熱
Well, get it hot enough.
快點
Now!
我說到今晚為止  我們得讓十輛車
I'm saying we got ten cars to move to the south track
移至南邊
by the end of the day,
所以我們不要
so let's not--
-解決了嗎  -解決了
- Took care of it? - Took care of it.
-你確定解決了  -是的
- You took care of it? - I took care of it!
發動機
Hey, the engine!
我們走  快讓這蠢東西動起來
Let's go! Roll this stupid thing.
邁爾斯  有麻煩
Miles, problem.
他被跳彈打死了
Ricochet got him.
喬  你負責火車
Joe, you're a train guy.
-你能開嗎  -我見過他開過一次
- Can you drive it? - I saw him do it once.
一次足夠了
Well, once is all we need.
你的機會來了  喬  我們走吧
Here's your chance, Joe. Let's go.
見鬼
Oh, hell.
-馬上  喬  -我知道
- Today, Joe! - I know!
快點
Come on!
阻止他們
Stop 'em!
別讓他們跑了
Don't let 'em get away!
-快點更好  喬  -我在努力
- Faster would be good, Joe. - I'm trying!
我得說  這挺有趣的
Got to admit that was kind of fun.
鳴汽笛  喬
Pull that whistle, Joe!
我們剛剛偷了輛火車
We just stole a train.
你在干什么
What are you looking at?
好像你不知道似的
As if you didn't know.
知道什么
Know what?
你說
You telling me...
你沒發現這里面的東西嗎
That you didn't find this in here?
艾德
Ed.
來
Here.
有什么緣由嗎
What's the occasion?
你讓我很幸福  瑪麗恩
You've made me happy, Marion.
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你  艾德
I love you too, Ed.
火車隨時到
Train will be here any minute.
我本該帶上所有的堿液
Then I'm supposed to take all this lye
中和芥氣
and neutralize the gas.
兜一圈  確保沒人跟著我們
Do a lap. Make sure we're alone.
跟邁爾斯是怎么回事
So what is it with him--Miles?
我爸看起來像是準備好要殺人一樣
I mean, my dad looks like he's ready to murder someone,
比以前欲望更強  自從
you know, more than usual, ever since...
自從邁爾斯把他趕走
Since Miles kicked him to the curb?
是啊
Well, yeah.
是怎么回事
So what's the story there?
不問  不說
Don't ask, don't tell.
我是認真問的
Come on, I'm serious.
孩子  說真的
Kid, seriously.
我這么些年來也一直問自己這個問題
I've been asking myself that question for years.
不論他們之間是怎樣變態的愛恨情仇
Whatever twisted love-hate, Cain-Abel brotherhood thing
兄弟之情
they got going,
都影響了他們的判斷力
it just clouds their judgment.
讓他們都彼此脆弱
Makes 'em both look weak.
這就是問題吧
That's a problem, isn't it?
只要邁爾斯在  我爸就無法
Dad will never get the republic back
奪回共和國
as long as miles is out there.
什么意思
What do you mean by that?
隨便聊聊
Just making conversation.
她要去哪
Where's she going?
她出去找更多實驗目標
She's going out to find more test subjects.
我們得阻止她  你知道吧
We have to stop her. You know that, right?
她的聽覺超好
She's got, like, super hearing.
我們試試
Let's see.
轉身吧  該死的機器人
Turn around, you damn robot.
我們會阻止你的
We're gonna stop you.
瑞秋
Rachel.
好了
Well, there you go.
也許它在普里西拉身體里越久  它就會
Maybe the longer it's in Priscilla, it's--
越受限制
I don't know-- more limited.
你去哪
Where are you going?
不  住手  住手  你在找什么
No, stop, stop. What are you looking for?
任何有用的東西
Anything that might help.
你想不想救普里西拉了
Do you want to save Priscilla or not?
當然想  你不明白
Of course I do. You don't understand.
那你告訴我
Then tell me.
它控制了我每一個舉動
This thing has been in control of every move I've made.
你沒法反抗  它知道一切
You can't fight it. It knows everything.
像是上帝一樣
It might as well be god.
你覺得我為什么會扇她耳光
Why do you think I slapped her?
因為你是瑞秋
'Cause you're Rachel.
那是個試驗
It was a test.
我想要看看她能不能預見到
I wanted to see if she could see it coming.
她不能
She can't.
那個賤人不是無所不知的
That bitch doesn't know everything.
她是個機器  是我們制造了她
She's a machine, and we made her.
我們可以出其不意
We can surprise her.
我們要救普里西拉
We're gonna save Priscilla.
我需要你的幫助
I need your help to do it.
快點  時間不多了
Come on. We don't have a lot of time.
卸下堿液
Unload the lye.
上馬車  我們走
Get on the wagon. Let's go.
邁爾斯
Hey, Miles.
沒錯  扔了手槍
That's right. Drop it.
過去
Back it up.
扔掉武器
Drop 'em.
我就知道我該殺了你的
I knew I should've just killed you.
內維爾
Neville?
不是吧
Really?
抱歉  邁爾斯
Sorry, Miles,
但我們要偷走你的火車
but we're stealing your train.
你到底要用芥氣干什么
What exactly do you plan to do with all that mustard gas?
我要把它直接開到華盛頓特區中心
I'm gonna drive it right into the heart of D.C.,
我要把那里燒為平地
and I'm gonna burn the place to the ground,
這是你該做的事
which is what you should be doing.
是我們該做的事
That's what we should be doing.
你和我
You and me.
我發誓  邁爾斯
I swear to god, Miles,
我不知道你怎么了
I don't know what happened to you.
我真的不知道
I genuinely don't understand.
我們走吧
Let's go, boys.
等下
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
她殺了我兒子
She murdered my boy.
湯姆
Tom.
你覺得我不會開槍殺你嗎  邁爾斯
You think I won't shoot through you, Miles?
快點上火車
Get on the train now!
湯姆  殺死杰森的不是她
Tom, she didn't kill Jason.
是愛國者們
Patriots did it.
我說了  上火車
I said get on the train.
否則我現在就殺了你
Or I'm gonna drop you right now.
我怎么一點都不驚訝呢
Well, why am I not surprised?
我們還有更重要的事
We got bigger fish to fry.
我發誓  你們倆
I swear to god, you two.
一切都是為了你寶貝的邁爾斯
Anything for your precious Miles.
是空的
It's empty.
芥氣呢
So where's the gas?
德州巡邏隊在這里干什么
What are Texas rangers doing here?
這是我要說的
That's my cue.
我們的孩子們
Our kids.
朋友們
Friends,
這是特別的一晚
this is a very special night,
我認為我們將永遠記住這一天
a memorial day I think we will long remember,
因為我們不只是在紀念這些
because we're not just honoring those U.S. troops
為國犧牲的美國軍人們
who paid the ultimate sacrifice,
我們也要向勇敢的德州巡邏隊表示敬意
we're paying tribute to the brave Texas rangers
他們也做出了犧牲
who have also fallen.
本著兩個國家
And so in this spirit
團結友好的精神
of the unity and friendship of our two nations,
我很榮幸介紹
it is my honor to introduce
兩位非常特別的嘉賓
two very special surprise guests--
德州共和國的總統
The president of the Texas Republic,
比爾·卡弗將軍
General Bill Carver,
以及美國總統杰克·戴維斯
and President Jack Davis of the United States.
你不冷嗎
The cold doesn't bother you?
應該冷嗎
Should it?
你在這里會非常快樂的
You're gonna be very happy here.
-快離開這里  -什么
- Get the hell out of here. - What?
走啊  快走
Go! Run!
不  回來
No! Come back!
你剛剛浪費了我一個實驗目標
You just cost me one of my subjects.
告訴我  我要怎樣取代她
So tell me, how am I gonna replace her?
怎樣  瑞秋
How, Rachel?
-她還好嗎  -還活著
- Is she okay? - She's alive.
普利西亞  聽我說
Priscilla, listen to me.
我知道你在
I know you're in there.
你得反抗  你得醒來
You have to fight this. You have to wake up.
我做到過  你也可以
I did it once. You can too.
不管你看到什么  都是在做夢
Whatever you're seeing, you're dreaming.
都不是真的  都是因為納米機器人
It's not real. It's the nano.
拜托
Please.
普利西亞  醒醒
Priscilla, wake up.
普利西亞  是你嗎
Priscilla, is that you?
你們真覺得這會有用嗎
Did you really think that would work?
現在我真的生氣了
Now I'm really angry.
你說每個人都會在是什么意思
What do you mean everybody's gonna be there?
音樂會
The concert.
所有人都會去政府大樓參加音樂會
Everyone's gonna be at the concert at the courthouse.
他們會把所有人集中到一個地方
So they're gonna have everybody together in one place.
失蹤的芥氣并不是自己走開的
And a load of missing gas that didn't just walk away.
他們會制造珍珠港事件
They're gonna have their Pearl Harbor,
只是不在奧斯丁市
just not in Austin.
會在這里  快走
It's gonna be here. Come on.
你在干什么  已經來不及了
What are you doing? You're too late.
停下  你要怎樣
Stop! What are you gonna do?
你要沖向一千噸芥氣嗎
You're gonna run straight into 1,000 tons of mustard gas.
如果我們不去  那就結束了
If we don't, it's over.
愛國者們就贏了
Patriots win it all.
你來不來
You in?
該死的
Damn it.
康納  我們走
Connor, let's go.
我說了  快上馬車
I said get on the wagon.
抱歉  我想我就不去那里了
Sorry. I think I'll pass on gas town.
我可不想自殺
I didn't sign up for suicide.
但你和邁爾斯  一起尋樂子吧
But you and Miles-- you two go have fun together.
回頭再給你算賬
I'll deal with you later.
在場的各位都知道
You folks down here sure know
要如何讓小伙子感到受到歡迎
how to make a fella feel welcome.
我很抱歉給你們帶來了
Now I have to apologize for springing
小小的驚喜
this little surprise on you,
但我可以保證這不只是為了吸引你們
but I can assure you this is not just showmanship,
但是如果我說
although I'd be lying
沒有這樣的成分  那就是撒謊
if I said that wasn't part of it.
不幸的是  這些日子
Unfortunately these days,
卡弗將軍和我
General Carver and I
有嚴重的安全問題要擔心
have very real security concerns.
咄咄逼人的好戰的加州
the aggressive and belligerent country of California
就在那里
is out there,
他們已經嘗試數次針對我們兩國的
and they have already attempted several terrorist acts
恐怖襲擊
against both of our nations,
在塞巴斯蒂安·門羅和
aided and abetted by Sebastian Monroe
邁爾斯·麥錫森的幫助下
and Miles Matheson.
所以我今天來到這里
That is why I am here today
站在卡弗將軍身邊
to stand beside Genera Carver
正式承諾將會提供武器和幫助
and officially pledge weapons and support
給予德州共和國對抗加州恐嚇
to the Texas Republic against this California menace.
現在  這些加州人
Now, these Californians--
他們站錯了位置
They're on the wrong side of history.
他們試圖撕毀
They're trying to rip apart
讓我們變得堅強的東西
the very thing that makes us strong.
兩分鐘
Two minutes.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我希望你沒看到這一切
I wish you hadn't seen this.
你這個混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你要殺死所有人
You're gonna kill everybody.
不是所有人
Not everybody.
我今晚說的話是真心的
I really meant what I said tonight.
我真的愛你
I do love you...
全心全意
With all my heart.
艾德
Ed.
因為這預示著一個美好的未來
Because it signified a bright future.
是無人能熄滅的光
And that's a light no one can put out.
團結  我們將不會失敗
United, we will not fail.
我們要說不
We say no!
我們用一個詞說出來
And we say it with one word.
那么今晚
So tonight,
讓我們全都記住說一句天佑英雄
let us all remember to say god bless our heroes,
德州共和國
the Republic of Texas,
天佑美利堅合眾國
and God bless the United States of America.